<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Alyve Health</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="traveled">Travelled in the last 24 hours</string>
    <string name="working_from">Working from</string>
    <string name="symptoms">Symptoms</string>
    <string name="consulted_doctor">Consulted Doctor</string>
    <string name="health_test_report_outcome">health test report outcome</string>
    <string name="view_risk_hots_near_you">View risks near you</string>
    <string name="your_recorded_actions_for_today">Your recorded actions</string>
    <string name="actions_mandated_by_your_organisation">Actions mandated by your organisation</string>
    <string name="organisation_guidance_and_communication">Organisation guidance and communication</string>
    <string name="helpful_information">Helpful information</string>
    <string name="english">English</string>
    <string name="hindi">हिन्दी</string>
    <string name="please_select_your_preferred_language">Please select your preferred language</string>
    <string name="access_code">Access code</string>
    <string name="corporate_email">Corporate email</string>
    <string name="login">Login</string>
    <string name="hello_and_welcome_immunity_health_protection_can_protect_you_and_your_colleagues_during_these_difficult_times">Hello and welcome! Immunity Employee Protect can secure you and your colleagues during these difficult times.</string>
    <string name="enter_email">Please enter email-id</string>
    <string name="enter_otp">Enter the OTP</string>
    <string name="resend_otp">Resend OTP</string>
    <string name="otp_has_been_sent_to_your_corporate_email">OTP has been sent to your corporate email and Mobile</string>
    <string name="please_answer">Please answer the following:</string>
    <string name="not_eleigible_for_app">Your age should be minimum 12 years</string>
    <string name="what_is_your_full_name">What is your full name?</string>
    <string name="what_is_your_date_of_birth">What is your date of birth?</string>
    <string name="you_are_a">You are a</string>
    <string name="male">Male</string>
    <string name="female">Female</string>
    <string name="non_binary">Non Binary</string>
    <string name="do_not_wish_to_disclose">Do not wish to disclose</string>
    <string name="whats_is_your_office_location">What is your office location?</string>
    <string name="whats_is_your_home_location">What is your home location?</string>
    <string name="do_you_have_any_of_the_following_health">Do you have any of the following health conditions? (Optional)</string>
    <string name="please_select_all_that_apply">Please select all that apply:</string>
    <string name="do_you_have_persons_older_than_50_years_living_in_your_household">Do you have persons older than 50 years living in your household? (Optional)</string>
    <string name="recovered">Recovered</string>
    <string name="positive">Positive</string>
    <string name="negative">Negative</string>
    <string name="what_is_your_health_infection_status">What is your health infection status?</string>
    <string name="whats_is_the_health_infection_status_of_your_household_members">Whats is the health infection status of your household members?</string>
    <string name="have_you_traveled_in_the_last_3_months">Have you travelled in the last 3 months? (Optional)</string>
    <string name="can_you_travel_to_your_work_place_in_your_own_vehicle_car_2_wheeler">Can you travel to your work place in your own vehicle (car/2 wheeler)? (Optional)</string>
    <string name="your_actions_for_today">Your actions for today</string>
    <string name="please_check_in_and_report_your_symptoms_daily_to_protect_yourself_and_your_colleagues">Please check-in and report your symptoms daily to protect yourself and your colleagues.</string>
    <string name="check_in_working_from">Check in - working from</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="office">Office</string>
    <string name="other_location">Other location</string>
    <string name="on_leave">On leave</string>
    <string name="under_isolation">Under isolation</string>
    <string name="under_quar">Under quar</string>
    <string name="enter_mobile_number">Enter mobile number</string>
    <string name="i_agree_the_terms_and_conditions">I agree the terms and conditions</string>
    <string name="terms_and_conditions">Terms and Conditions</string>
    <string name="please_wait">Please wait..!</string>
    <string name="have_you_traveled">Have you travelled in the last 24 hours?</string>
    <string name="have_you_already_consulted_a_doctor">Have you already consulted a doctor?</string>
    <string name="has_your_doctor_recommended_health_19_test">Has your doctor recommended health-19 test?</string>
    <string name="what_was_the_health_test_outcome">What was the health test outcome?</string>
    <string name="personal_details">Personal Details</string>
    <string name="button_connect">Connect</string>
    <string name="button_disconnect">Disconnect</string>
    <string name="title_devices">Devices</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="action_about">About</string>
    <string name="app_author">Author : Donato Rimenti</string>
    <string name="app_version">Version: 1.0.1</string>
    <string name="app_info">Project</string>
    <string name="app_descrip">Simple app for handling Bluetooth discovery and pairing.</string>
    <string name="device_discovery_started">Looking for nearby devices…</string>
    <string name="device_already_paired">This device is already paired!</string>
    <string name="device_pairing_success">Device successfully paired!</string>
    <string name="enabling_bluetooth">Turning on Bluetooth and looking for devices…</string>
    <string name="device_discovery_stopped">Device discovery cancelled</string>
    <string name="empty_list_message">No nearby devices found. Tap on the bottom-right button to start a new device discovery.</string>
    <string name="bluetooth_not_available_message">It seems that this device doesn\'t have a Bluetooth controller available. \nBlue Pair works only with Bluetooth, so please try again on a different device. \nThe app will be now terminated.</string>
    <string name="bluetooth_not_available_title">Bluetooth not available</string>
    <string name="txt_search">Search User</string>
    <string name="where_have_you_traveled_in_last_24_hours">Where have you travelled in the last 24 hours?</string>
    <string name="mode_of_transport">What was the mode of transport?</string>
    <string name="within_the_city">Within the city</string>
    <string name="outside_of_city">Outside of city</string>
    <string name="work">Work</string>
    <string name="pickup_location">Search Places</string>
    <string name="title_activity_cluster_map_track">Map</string>
    <string name="private_transport">Private transport</string>
    <string name="public_transport">Public transport</string>
    <string name="terms_and_cond">When you use the Immunity app, information is collected from and about you. Imagine Health Pvt. Ltd. (“We”) is committed to protecting the security of this information and protecting your privacy. This privacy policy sets out the details of the personal information collected, the manner in which it is collected, by whom as well as the purposes for which it is used. Your registration confirms your acceptance of the terms of this Privacy Policy and your use of the App signifies your continued acceptance thereof. This Privacy Policy may be revised from time to time and you will be notified of all such changes. In order to use the App, you will be required to consent to the terms of the Privacy Policy as revised from time to time.</string>
    <string name="email_validation">Couldn\'t find Immunity account for your organization</string>
    <string name="first_terms_and_cond"><![CDATA[1. INFORMATION COLLECTED AND MANNER OF COLLECTION \n When you register on the app, the following information is collected from you and stored securely on the cloud – (i) name; (ii) phone number & email address; (iii) date of birth; (iv) gender; (v) residence and office location; (vi) travel history; (vii) medical history of self and parents (viii) whether you have persons over 50 years of age living in your household (ix) whether you can commute in your private vehicle; \n  Additionally, on a daily basis (or whenever you wish to submit), the following information would be collected from you – (i) Check-in location – home / office / other, (ii) Symptoms and follow up (including whether you have consulted a doctor) and (iii) Travel history – domestic or inter-city. Proximity information (obtained through bluetooth interactions of smart phones near each other) would also be captured whenever your bluetooth is switched on. Information pertaining to your location will be captured on the basis of the permissions you grant the app (Never / Always / While using the app). \n You agree that we may collect and use technical information about your device, system and application software, and peripherals, that is gathered periodically to facilitate the provision of software updates, product support and other services like proximity calculation with other devices. \n  Finally, your corporate community manager (or a delegate) might assign actions to you on a daily basis (or whenever they wish to) – information pertaining to these actions as well will be securely stored on our cloud servers.\n]]></string>
    <string name="second_terms_and_cond">2. USE OF INFORMATION \n The personal information collected from or about you, will be shared only with the manager of your corporate community (either the CEO or CHRO or somebody they delegate to). Your information will only be used for the purpose of providing guidance to you and to protect you. Information pertaining to your symptoms will be used anonymously to depict a symptoms map.  Your corporate community manager will not have access to your location or device information on a personally identifiable basis. Information related to proximity can be used by your community manager for the purpose of contact tracing only with the intention to safeguard you in case you have come in contact with an infected or symptomatic person. Such information may be shared by your community manager with relevant Government authorities based on Government guidelines and policy.  The mobile number and email address that you provide at the time of registration may be used to communicate with you through SMS, email, push notifications or other such means to inform you about your health status or to remind you to enter your daily actions, and to provide you such other notifications as may be required. In case your information needs to be used for any other purpose other than that mentioned in this clause or needs to be shared with third parties, we will seek explicit consent for the same.\n</string>
    <string name="third_terms_and_cond">"3. RETENTION \n All information provided at the time of registration will be retained for as long as your account remains in existence and for such period thereafter as required for the purposes for which the information may lawfully be used or is otherwise required under any other law for the time being in force. Nothing set out herein shall apply to the anonymized, aggregated datasets generated by the personal data of registered users of the App or any reports, heat maps or other visualization created using such datasets. \n All information collected on periodic basis (as covered in section1), will be retained for a period of 60 days from the date of collection after which it will be purged.\n "</string>
    <string name="fourth_terms_and_cond">"4.RIGHTS \n As a registered user, you have the right to access your profile at any time to add, remove or modify any information that you have supplied. You also have the right to delete your account at any time. \n"</string>
    <string name="fifth_terms_and_cond">5. DATA SECURITY \n The App is equipped with standard security features to protect the confidentiality and security of your information. We shall maintain and implement reasonable and appropriate security procedures consistent with prevailing industry standards and all applicable laws to protect personal data from any unauthorized access or use. In the event of a security breach, we will use diligent efforts to promptly remedy and prevent any continuation or recurrence of any unauthorized access or use. We shall maintain adequate physical controls and password protections for any server or system on which any Data may reside, encrypt any Data that is in transmission, and encrypt any Data located on any storage media. \n</string>
    <string name="sixth_terms_and_cond">6. GRIEVANCES \n If you have any concerns or questions in relation to this policy, please address them to grievances. protect@immunityhealth.me \n The content is not intended to be a substitute for professional medical advice, diagnosis or treatment. Always seek the advice of a medical expert or other qualified health providers for any questions you may have regarding a medical condition. We are not accountable for the specific actions assigned to you by your corporate community manager or by a delegate. Any symptom maps or other depictions are intended to assist you and protect you – please use the information as per your discretion.\n</string>
    <string name="seventh_terms_and_cond">7. Limitation of liability \n We value your trust in providing us your Personal Information, thus we are striving to use commercially acceptable means of protecting it. But no method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure and reliable, and we cannot guarantee its absolute security. You agree and acknowledge that we will not be liable for any claims in relation to the use of the App, including but not limited to (a) your inability to access or use the App or the services; (b) the failure of the App or the services to accurately identify persons in your proximity; (c) any unauthorised access to your information or modification thereof. \n</string>
    <string name="hr_agreement">This is an agreement between you or the entity that you represent (hereinafter “you” or “your”) and Imagine Health Pvt. Ltd. (hereinafter “us” or “we” or “our”) governing your use of our software.</string>
    <string name="accept_terms_agreement">You can accept the Terms by checking a checkbox or clicking on a button indicating your acceptance of the terms or by actually using the services.</string>
    <string name="description_terms_agreement">Our software enables you to assess health risks at an individual employee level and communicate with your employees in a segmented and/or individualized manner.</string>
    <string name="organization_terms_agreement">When you register with us, you are registering as an organization community manager or administrator. The administrators will have the right to configure the services based on your requirements and manage end users in your organization account. \n You are responsible for i) ensuring confidentiality of your organization information and data, ii) delegating to competent individuals as delegated administrators for managing your organization account, and iii) ensuring that all activities that occur in connection with your organization account comply with this Agreement. You understand that we are not responsible for account administration and internal management of the services for you. You are responsible for taking necessary steps for ensuring that your organization does not lose control of the administrator accounts. You are responsible for all activities that occur in your user account and you agree to inform us immediately of any unauthorized use of your user account by email to help@immunityhealth.me. You agree not to hold us liable for the consequences of any action taken by us in good faith in this regard</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy">When you use the Immunity dashboard, information is collected from and about your organization. We are committed to protecting the security of this information and protecting your privacy. This privacy policy sets out the details of the personal information collected, the manner in which it is collected, by whom as well as the purposes for which it is used. Your registration confirms your acceptance of the terms of this Privacy Policy and your use of the portal signifies your continued acceptance thereof. This Privacy Policy may be revised from time to time and you will be notified of all such changes. In order to use the portal, you will be required to consent to the terms of the Privacy Policy as revised from time to time.</string>
    <string name="inform_collected_terms_and_cond">1. INFORMATION COLLECTED AND MANNER OF COLLECTION \n When you register your company on the portal, the following information is collected from you and stored securely on the cloud – (i) your corporate email; (ii) your mobile number; (iii) your full name; (iv) name of your organization; (v) number of employees in your organization; (vi) your designation; (vii) copy of your business card and (viii) url of  your linked in profile (optional). \n Upon registering, you will have the option to upload details of your employees where the following data would be captured for each employee – (i) Full name, (ii) Email id, (iii) Mobile number and (iv) Department. Additionally, on a daily basis (or whenever you wish to), you have the option to create and assign actions to the onboarded employees. These details would be stored securely in 3rd party cloud servers. \n  Furthermore, the portal would leverage information shared by employees on the Immunity app (with their explicit consent as per the terms and conditions specified in the app)\n</string>
    <string name="use_of_inform"><![CDATA[2. USE OF INFORMATION \n By registering on the portal, you designate yourself as the corporate community manager for your corporate. Only you (or somebody you delegate to) will have the access to the information and details shared by the employees of your corporate. Such information may be shared by you with relevant Government authorities based on Government guidelines and policy.   You will not have access to location information of your employees on a personally identifiable basis. The mobile number and email address that you provide at the time of registration may be used to communicate with you through SMS, email, push notifications or other such means to inform you about the status of activity in your organization or to provide you such other notifications as may be required.\n]]></string>
    <string name="use_of_retention">3. RETENTION \n All information provided at the time of registration will be retained for as long as your account remains in existence and for such period thereafter as required for the purposes for which the information may lawfully be used or is otherwise required under any other law for the time being in force. Nothing set out herein shall apply to the anonymized, aggregated datasets generated by the personal data of registered users of the App or any reports, heat maps or other visualization created using such datasets. \n All information collected on periodic basis (as covered in section1), will be retained for a period of 60 days from the date of collection after which it will be purged from the server.\n</string>
    <string name="use_of_rights">4. RIGHTS \n As a registered user, you have the right to access your profile at any time to add, remove or modify any information that you have supplied. You also have the right to delete your account at any time.\n</string>
    <string name="use_of_data_security"><![CDATA[5. DATA SECURITY \n The portal is equipped with standard security features to protect the confidentiality and security of your information. We shall maintain and implement reasonable and appropriate security procedures consistent with prevailing industry standards and all applicable laws to protect personal data from any unauthorized access or use. In the event of a security breach, we will use diligent efforts to promptly remedy and prevent any continuation or recurrence of any unauthorized access or use. We shall maintain adequate physical controls and password protections for any server or system on which any Data may reside, encrypt any Data that is in transmission, and encrypt any Data located on any storage media.]]></string>
    <string name="use_of_grievances">"6. GRIEVANCES \n If you have any concerns or questions in relation to this policy, please address them to grievances.healthprotect@immunityhealth.me \n The content is not intended to be a substitute for professional medical advice, diagnosis or treatment. Always seek the advice of a medical expert or other qualified health providers for any questions you may have regarding a medical condition. We are not accountable for the actions assigned to your employees, the responsibility for which lies solely with you. \n</string>
    <string name="use_of_liability">7. Limitation of liability \n We value your trust in providing us your Personal Information, thus we are striving to use commercially acceptable means of protecting it. But no method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure and reliable, and we cannot guarantee its absolute security. You agree and acknowledge that we will not be liable for any claims in relation to the use of our software, including but not limited to (a) your inability to access or use of our software; (b) the failure of our software to accurately identify persons in proximity to your employees; (c) any unauthorised access to the information of your organization or modification thereof. \n</string>
    <string name="data_ownership">We respect your right to ownership of content created or stored by you. You own the content created or stored by you. Unless specifically permitted by you, your use of the services does not grant us the license to use, reproduce, adapt, modify, publish or distribute the content created by you or stored in your user account for our commercial, marketing or any similar purpose.</string>
    <string name="data_communication">The Service may include certain communications from us, such as service announcements, administrative messages and newsletters. You understand that these communications shall be considered part of using the services.</string>
    <string name="restricion_desc">In addition to all other terms and conditions of this Agreement, you shall not: (i) transfer the services or otherwise make it available to any third party; (ii) provide any service based on the services without prior written permission; (iii) publish any personal or confidential information belonging to any person or entity without obtaining consent from such person or entity; (iv) use the Services in any manner that could damage, disable, overburden, impair or harm any server, network, computer system, resource belonging to us; (v) violate any applicable local, state, national or international law; and (vi) create a false identity to mislead any person as to the identity or origin of any communication (vii) violate the confidentiality / privacy rights of your employees</string>
    <string name="warranties_desc">You expressly understand and agree that the use of the services is at your sole risk. The services are provided on an as-is-and-as-available basis. We expressly disclaim all warranties of any kind, whether express or implied, including, but not limited to, the implied warranties of merchantability and fitness for a particular purpose. We make no warranty that the services will be uninterrupted, timely, secure, or error free. Use of any material downloaded or obtained through the use of the services shall be at your own discretion and risk and you will be solely responsible for any damage to your computer system, mobile telephone, wireless device or data that results from the use of the services or the download of any such material. No advice or information, whether written or oral, obtained by you from us, its employees or representatives shall create any warranty not expressly stated in the terms.</string>
    <string name="liability_desc">You agree that we shall, in no event, be liable for any consequential, incidental, indirect, special, punitive, or other loss or damage whatsoever or for loss of business profits, business interruption, computer failure, loss of business information, or other loss arising out of or caused by your use of or inability to use the service, even if we have been advised of the possibility of such damage.</string>
    <string name="indeminification">You agree to indemnify and hold harmless us, our officers, directors, employees, suppliers, and affiliates, from and against any losses, damages, fines and expenses (including attorney\'s fees and costs) arising out of or relating to any claims that you have used the Services in violation of another party\'s rights, in violation of any law, in violations of any provisions of the Terms, or any other claim related to your use of the Services, except where such use is authorized by us.</string>
    <string name="arbitration">Any controversy or claim arising out of or relating to the Terms shall be settled by binding arbitration in accordance with the commercial arbitration rules of India. Any such controversy or claim shall be arbitrated on an individual basis, and shall not be consolidated in any arbitration with any claim or controversy of any other party. The decision of the arbitrator shall be final and unappealable. The arbitration shall be conducted in India and judgment on the arbitration award may be entered into any court having jurisdiction thereof. Notwithstanding anything to the contrary, we may at any time seek injunctions or other forms of equitable relief from any court of competent jurisdiction.</string>
    <string name="suspension"><![CDATA[We may suspend your user account or temporarily disable access to whole or part of any service in the event of any suspected illegal activity, extended periods of inactivity or requests by law enforcement or other government agencies. Objections to suspension or disabling of user accounts should be made to grievances@immunityhealth.me within thirty days of being notified about the suspension. We may terminate a suspended or disabled user account after thirty days. We will also terminate your user account on your request. In addition, we reserve the right to terminate your user account and deny the services upon reasonable belief that you have violated the Terms. You have the right to terminate your user account if we breach our obligations under these Terms. Termination of user account will include denial of access to all services, deletion of information in your user account such as your email address and deletion of all data in your user account. \n \n \n]]></string>
    <string name="not_working">Not working</string>
    <string name="you_are">You are :</string>
    <string name="i_don_t_know">I don\'t Know</string>
    <string name="do_either_of_your_parents_have_the_following_health_conditions">Do either of your parents have the following health conditions? (Optional)</string>
    <string name="high_bp_hypertension">High BP/Hypertension</string>
    <string name="pre_diabetes_diabetes">Pre-Diabetes / Diabetes</string>
    <string name="high_cholesterol_triglyceride">High Cholesterol / Triglyceride</string>
    <string name="asthma_copd">Asthma/COPD</string>
    <string name="other_chronic_health_condition">Other Chronic Health Condition</string>
    <string name="domestic">Domestic</string>
    <string name="international">International</string>
    <string name="dashboard">Dashboard</string>
    <string name="scan">Scan</string>
    <string name="noticeboard">Noticeboard</string>
    <string name="or">OR</string>
    <string name="search_location">Search location</string>
    <string name="done">done</string>
    <string name="email_address">Email address</string>
    <string name="mobile_number">Mobile Number</string>
    <string name="date_of_birth">Date of birth</string>
    <string name="edit_profile">Edit Profile</string>
    <string name="with_all">With All</string>
    <string name="i_don_t_agree">i don\'t agree</string>
    <string name="corporate_subscriber">Corporate Subscriber</string>
    <string name="insights">Insights</string>
    <string name="colleagues_within_your_organization_have_self_reported_symptoms_today">Colleagues within your organization have self reported symptoms today</string>
    <string name="colleagues_near_you_have_self_reported_symptoms_today">Colleagues near you have self reported symptoms today</string>
    <string name="proximity_violations_by_you_on">Proximity violations by you on </string>
    <string name="no">No</string>
    <string name="yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="download_aarogya_setu_app_and_check_your_status_regularly">Download Aarogya Setu app and check your status regularly</string>
    <string name="cover_your_face_at_all_times">Cover your face at all times</string>
    <string name="maintain_6_feet_distance_from_your_colleagues_at_all_times">Maintain 6 feet distance from your colleagues at all times</string>
    <string name="avoid_touching_your_face_sanitize_your_hands_at_regular_intervals">Avoid touching your face; sanitize your hands at regular intervals</string>
    <string name="report_your_symptoms_daily_do_not_come_to_office_if_you_feel_unwell">Report your symptoms daily; do not come to office if you feel unwell</string>
    <string name="report_symptoms">Report Symptoms</string>
    <string name="fever">Fever</string>
    <string name="dry_cough">Dry cough</string>
    <string name="breathing_difficulty">Breathing difficulty</string>
    <string name="none">None</string>
    <string name="profile">Profile</string>
    <string name="help_and_support">Help and Support</string>
    <string name="logout">Logout</string>
    <string name="enter_subject">Enter Subject</string>
    <string name="enter_description">Enter Description</string>
    <string name="cancel">CANCEL</string>
    <string name="submit">SUBMIT</string>
    <string name="save_profile">Save profile</string>
    <string name="success">Success</string>
    <string name="inactive">Inactive QR Code</string>
    <string name="invalid">Invalid QR Code</string>
    <string name="retry">Retry</string>
    <string name="ok">OKAY</string>
    <string name="otpmobile">OTP has been sent to</string>
    <string name="otpemail">OTP has been sent to your corporate email</string>
    <string name="iagree">I agree</string>
    <string name="edit_more_details"><u>More Information</u></string>
    <string name="none_of_the_above">None of the above</string>
    <string name="pleasesearch">Please search the location</string>
    <string name="safe">Ok. Take precaution</string>
    <string name="care">Be alert. Take care</string>
    <string name="check">Check</string>
    <string name="safe_take_care">Safe / Take Care</string>
    <string name="check_before_you_leave">Check before you leave</string>
    <string name="this_information_is_from_public_sources_and_please_be_careful_at_all_times">* This information is from public sources, please be careful at all times</string>
    <string name="update_message">Update</string>
    <string name="update_now">Now</string>
    <string name="add_geofences">Add geofences</string>
    <string name="remove_geofences">Remove geofences</string>
    <string name="geofences_added">Geofences added</string>
    <string name="geofences_removed">Geofences removed</string>
    <string name="geofence_not_available">Geofence service is not available now</string>
    <string name="geofence_too_many_geofences">Your app has registered too many geofences</string>
    <string name="geofence_too_many_pending_intents">You have provided too many PendingIntents to the addGeofences() call</string>
    <string name="unknown_geofence_error">Unknown error: the Geofence service is not available now</string>
    <string name="geofence_transition_invalid_type">Geofence transition error: invalid transition type %1$d</string>
    <string name="geofence_transition_entered">Entered</string>
    <string name="geofence_transition_exited">Exited</string>
    <string name="unknown_geofence_transition">Unknown Transition</string>
    <string name="geofence_transition_notification_text">Your Auto Check-in is Successfull</string>
    <string name="insufficient_permissions">Insufficient permissions.</string>
    <string name="permission_rationale">Location permission is needed for core functionality</string>
    <string name="permission_denied_explanation">Permission was denied, but is needed for corefunctionality.</string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="discover">Discover</string>
    <string name="read">Read</string>
    <string name="watch">Watch</string>
    <string name="think">Think</string>
    <string name="manage">Manage</string>
    <string name="protect">Protect</string>
    <string name="prevent">Prevent</string>
    <string name="event">Event</string>
    <string name="okk">OK</string>
    <string name="bealert">Be alert</string>
    <string name="welcome_to_the_world_s_first_personal_health_assistant_protect_yourself_and_your_communities_track_your_vitals_activity_and_environment_resume_your_life">Welcome to the World\'s first personal health assistant. Protect yourself and your communities. Track your vitals, activity and environment. Resume your life!</string>
    <string name="have_you_been_in_proximity_with_someone_who_is_showing_symptoms">Have you been in proximity with someone who is showing symptoms?</string>
    <string name="communities_are_your_support_system_research_proves_that_communities_can_inspire_you_to_achieve_your_health_goals_faster">Communities are your support system. Research proves that communities can inspire you to achieve your health goals faster. Join your community now.</string>
    <string name="welcome_to_your_personal_health_ecosystem_protect_yourself_and_your_communities_track_your_vitals_activity_and_environment_resume_your_life">Welcome to your personal health ecosystem. Protect yourself and your communities. Track your vitals, activity and environment. Resume your life.</string>
    <string name="enter_your_corporate_email_to_join_your_corporate_community_optional">Enter your corporate email to join your corporate community. (Optional)</string>
    <string name="goal">Goal</string>
    <string name="step_size">Step size</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="account">Account</string>
    <string name="goal_summary">Current goal: %,d steps</string>
    <string name="step_size_summary">Current step size: %1$.2f %2$s</string>
    <string name="sign_in">Sign in with your Google account to use the Achievements and Leaderboards features</string>
    <string name="signed_in">Signed in as %s</string>
    <string name="export_summary">Save your data in a .csv file</string>
    <string name="export_title">Export/Backup</string>
    <string name="import_summary">Imports previously saved data</string>
    <string name="import_title">Import/Restore</string>
    <string name="notification">Show notification</string>
    <string name="set_goal">Set goal</string>
    <string name="set_step_size">Set step size</string>
    <string name="sign_out">Sign out</string>
    <string name="file_cant_read">Error: %s can not be read</string>
    <string name="error_file">Error accessing the file: %s</string>
    <string name="error_external_storage_not_available">Error: External storage not available</string>
    <string name="data_saved">Data saved in %s</string>
    <string name="entries_imported">%d entries imported</string>
    <string name="entries_ignored">%d entries were ignored as they did not contain valid data</string>
    <string name="entries_overwritten">%d entries were overwritten with imported data</string>
    <string name="sign_in_necessary">Sign in necessary</string>
    <string name="please_sign_in_with_your_google_account">Please sign in with your Google+ account to use this feature.</string>
    <string name="steps">steps</string>
    <string name="text_color">Text color:</string>
    <string name="background_color">Background color:</string>
    <string name="achievements">Achievements</string>
    <string name="leaderboard">Leaderboard</string>
    <string name="faq">FAQ</string>
    <string name="goal_reached_notification">Goal reached! %s steps and counting</string>
    <string name="notification_text">%s steps to go</string>
    <string name="total">Total</string>
    <string name="notification_title">Glad to see you step into your shoes.</string>
    <string name="your_progress_will_be_shown_here_soon">Your progress will be shown here soon</string>
    <string name="average">Average</string>
    <string name="record">Record</string>
    <string name="total_last_7_days">Total last 7 days</string>
    <string name="average_last_7_days">Average last 7 days</string>
    <string name="total_this_month">Total this month</string>
    <string name="average_this_month">Average this month</string>
    <string name="file_already_exists">File already exists. Are you sure you want to overwrite it?</string>
    <string name="about_text_links">This app was created by Thomas Hoffmann and updated by Projectworlds  and uses <a href="https://projectworlds.in">Projectworlds</a> by Yugesh Verma  This App is open source! .\n\n</string>
    <string name="about_app_version">App version: %s</string>
    <string name="since">Since %s</string>
    <string name="start">Start</string>
    <string name="stop">Stop</string>
    <string name="close">close</string>
    <string name="no_split_active">No split counter active. Click start to count the steps from now on</string>
    <string name="split_count">Split count</string>
    <string name="no_sensor">Sensor not found</string>
    <string name="no_sensor_explain">This app requires a dedicated hardware step sensor - which your device does not have. This app won\'t run on your device.</string>
    <string name="permission_external_storage">No permission to access external storage</string>
    <string name="notification_settings">Notification settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_welcome">Home Screen</string>
    <string name="next">NEXT</string>
    <string name="skip">SKIP</string>


    <string name="slide_1_title">Hello Food!</string>
    <string name="slide_1_desc">The easiest way to order food from your favourite restaurant!</string>

    <string name="slide_2_title">Movie Tickets</string>
    <string name="slide_2_desc">Book movie tickets for your family and friends!</string>

    <string name="slide_3_title">Great Discounts</string>
    <string name="slide_3_desc">Best discounts on every single service we offer!</string>

    <string name="slide_4_title">World Travel</string>
    <string name="slide_4_desc">Book tickets of any transportation and travel the world!</string>

    <string name="play_again_desc">To see the welcome slider again, goto Settings -> apps -> welcome slider -> clear data</string>
    <string name="play_again">Play Again</string>
    <string name="default_notification_channel_id">0</string>


</resources>
